Crusade for Opportunity Records
Crusade for Opportunity Records
- Neighborhood Centers
  - Staff files
    - Jones, Shirley files, Assistant Director of Community Services
      - Campership information, 1965 (Box 129)
      - Catholic Charities, 1965 (Box 129)
      - Community services positions, 1966 (Box 129)
      - Connie Timberlake, Neighborhood Advancement Center, correspondence, 1965 (Box 129)
      - Contact and referral, 1965 (Box 129)
      - Contract services, 1965 (Box 129)
      - Copies of local expense sheets that have been submitted, 1965 (Box 129)
      - Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 129)
      - Credit union, 1965 (Box 129)
      - Current programs of Help Center, 1965 (Box 129)
      - Day care services, 1966 (Box 129)
      - Division meeting minutes, 1964-1965 (Box 129)
      - East Side, advisory council, 1964-1965 (Box 129)
      - Education memos, 1965-1966 (Box 129)
      - Employment, 1965-1966 (Box 129)
      - Field operations job description, 1966 (Box 129)
      - Films - family life, 1963 (Box 129)
      - Francesco Rodriguez, 1965 (Box 129)
      - Frank Reissman essay, 1965 (Box 129)
      - Homemaker, 1965 (Box 129)
      - Housing, 1964-1965 (Box 130)
      - Huntington Family Center, 1965 (Box 130)
      - Information and referral services, 1966 (Box 130)
      - Inner city day camp, 1965 (Box 130)
      - Interview with Betty King (conducted by Nat Auerbach), 1965 (Box 130)
      - Juvenile delinquency clippings, articles, 1962-1964 (Box 130)
      - Library materials, 1965-1966 (Box 130)
      - Manpower Development Training Act program, 1963-1965 (Box 130)
      - Medicare alert, 1966 (Box 130)
      - Mental health aide, undated (Box 130)
      - Minna Buck correspondence, 1966 (Box 130)
      - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 130)
      - Multi-problem practitioners, 1965 (Box 130)
      - Neighborhood Board, 1965-1966 (Box 130)
      - Neighborhood board elections, 1966 (Box 130)
      - Neighborhood center model, 1966 (Box 130)
      - New York State employment service, 1965 (Box 130)
      - Prospective staff applicants, 1965-1966 (Box 130)
      - Referral forms, 1965-1966 (Box 130)
      - Research department memos, 1966 (Box 130)
      - Research intake forms, 1965 (Box 130)
      - Restorative services subcommittee, 1965 (Box 130)
      - Robert Mayer, 1965 (Box 130)
      - Rochester poverty program, 1966 (Box 131)
      - Scholarship committee, 1965 (Box 131)
      - School district, 1965 (Box 131)
      - Skill center, 1965 (Box 131)
      - Staff correspondence and memos, 1964-1966 (Box 131)
      - Summer program budgets, 1965 (Box 131)
      - Summer recreation, 1965-1966 (Box 131)
      - Supervisor's meeting, 1965 (Box 131)
      - Syracuse University, 1965-1966 (Box 131)
      - Tallman Center, 1965-1966 (Box 131)
      - Tallman day camp program, 1965 (Box 131)
      - Team meeting, 1965-1966 (Box 131)
      - Teen council, 1965-1966 (Box 131)
      - Theatre Training Program, undated (Box 131)
      - United Community Chest and Council of Onondaga, Inc., general, 1965-1966 (Box 131)
      - United Church Women, 1965 (Box 131)
      - Urban renewal, 1965-1966 (Box 131)
      - Volunteer Center, 1965 (Box 131)
      - West Side neighborhood meetings, 1965 (Box 131)
      - Youth work program, 1965-1966 (Box 131)
  - Tallman Center
    - Annual reports, 1965 (Box 131)
    - Car pool, 1967 (Box 131)
    - Child care committee, 1967 (Box 131)
    - Consumer survey, 1967 (Box 131)
    - Co-op committee, 1967 (Box 131)
    - Day camp committee, 1967 (Box 131)
    - Education committee, 1967 (Box 131)
    - Employment committee, 1966 (Box 131)
    - Equipment, 1967 (Box 131)
    - Expenditures, 1966 (Box 131)
    - Fact sheets, 1966 (Box 131)
    - Fact sheet and discussion guide (Box 131)
    - Finance committee, 1967 (Box 131)
    - Housing committee, 1967 (Box 131)
    - Information and referral committee, 1967 (Box 131)
    - Investigating committee, 1967 (Box 131)
    - Job opportunities, 1967 (Box 131)
    - Job orders for mimeographing, ditto, azograph, etc., 1966-1967; 8 folders (Box 132)
    - Joint training and writing, committee for childcare, 1966 (Box 132)
    - Legal service committee, 1967 (Box 132)
    - Mailing lists, 1967 (Box 132)
    - Meeting minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 132)
    - Memos, 1967 (Box 132)
    - Mobilization for Youth, Inc., 1966 (Box 132)
    - Monthly reports, 1967 (Box 132)
    - Morning reports, 1967 (Box 132)
    - Neighborhood board elections, Oct 1966 (Box 132)
    - Neighborhood board elections and progress report, 1967 (Box 132)
    - Neighborhood board meeting, 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box 133)
    - Neighborhood board meeting minutes, 1965-1966; 2 folders (Box 133)
    - Neighborhood board, memos and correspondence, 1967 (Box 133)
    - Newspaper, 1967 (Box 133)
    - Personnel, memos, 1967 (Box 133)
    - Planning committee, 1967; 2 folders (Box 133)
    - Pre-school committee, 1967 (Box 133)
    - Program coordinator, 1966 (Box 133)
    - Programs operative, 1967 (Box 133)
    - Purchasing, 1967 (Box 133)
    - Recreation committee, 1967 (Box 133)
    - Representatives for panel discussion, 1966 (Box 133)
    - Requisitions, 1967 (Box 133)
    - Sewing program, 1967 (Box 133)
    - Six weeks report, 1967 (Box 133)
    - Staff assignments, 1967 (Box 133)
    - Staff cars, 1967 (Box 133)
    - Staff committee assignments, 1967 (Box 133)
    - Staff meetings, 1967 (Box 133)
    - Strategy committee for employment, 1967 (Box 133)
    - Study center report, 1967 (Box 133)
    - Tallman area, 1966 (Box 133)
    - Tallman area news, 1967 (Box 133)
    - Tallman election results, 1966 (Box 133)
    - Tallman neighborhood board, 1965-1966; 2 folders (Box 133)
    - Tallman neighborhood elections, 1966 (Box 133)
    - Teen council, 1965-1966 (Box 133)
    - Teen council planning committee, undated (Box 133)
    - Telephones, 1967 (Box 133)
    - Training correspondence, general, 1967 (Box 133)
    - Welfare committee, 1967 (Box 133)
  - West Side Center
    - Action area planning, 1964-1967 (Box 134)
    - Advisory council (to become Neighborhood Board), 1965 (Box 134)
    - "Are you willing?" flyer, undated (Box 134)
    - Bicycle tripping program, applications, undated (Box 134)
    - Campaign election, 1966 (Box 134)
    - Camperships, 1966 (Box 134)
    - Camperships applications, 1965-1966 (Box 134)
    - Camp placement follow-up information, 1965 (Box 134)
    - Community service members, 1967 (Box 134)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 134)
    - Documentation, 1965 (Box 134)
    - Duplicate order sheets, 1965 (Box 134)
    - Easter week bus trips, 1965 (Box 134)
    - Education committee, 1965-1967; 2 folders (Box 134)
    - Election budget, 1967 (Box 134)
    - Election candidates, undated (Box 134)
    - Election rally, 1966 (Box 134)
    - Election volunteers, 1966 (Box 134)
    - Employment committee, 1966-1967 (Box 134)
    - Equipment, 1967 (Box 134)
    - Equipment inventory, 1967 (Box 134)
    - Fact sheets, 1966; 3 folders (Box 134)
    - Field reports, 1966 (Box 134)
    - Flyers, 1967 (Box 362)
    - Full reports, 1966 (Box 134)
    - Full and part time staff and NYC trainees, 1967 (Box 134)
    - Gladys Smith, memos, 1967 (Box 134)
    - Gladys Smith, news clippings, 1967 (Box 134)
    - Head Start committee members, 1967 (Box 134)
    - Housing committee, 1967 (Box 134)
    - Interagency, 1965-1966 (Box 134)
    - Interagency summer program, 1965; 2 folders (Box 135)
    - Jefferson Park Camp, 1966 (Box 135)
    - Job orders for copies, 1967 (Box 135)
    - Job orders for copies, 1967 (Box 362)
    - Joint campership meeting minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 135)
    - Joint legal services meeting minutes, 1967 (Box 135)
    - Meeting minutes, 1966 (Box 135)
    - Mobile classroom, 1966 (Box 135)
    - Monthly reports, 1966-1967 (Box 135)
    - Morning reports, 1967 (Box 135)
    - Neighborhood board, 1966 (Box 135)
    - Neighborhood board agendas, 1965-1967 (Box 135)
    - Neighborhood board annual report, circa 1966 (Box 135)
    - Neighborhood board campaign election and election registration lists, 1966-1967 (Box 135)
    - Neighborhood board committees, 1965-1966 (Box 135)
    - Neighborhood board and committee members, 1967 (Box 135)
    - Neighborhood board elections, 1966; 2 folders (Box 135)
    - Neighborhood Board election campaign correspondence, 1967 (Box 135)
    - Neighborhood board elections, organizations, 1965 (Box 135)
    - Neighborhood board information, 1965-1966 (Box 135)
    - Neighborhood board meeting, 1966 (Box 135)
    - Neighborhood board meeting minutes, 1965-1966 (Box 135)
    - Neighborhood board meeting minutes, 1965-1967; 5 folders (Box 136)
    - Neighborhood board meeting minutes with mimeograph orders [stencils discarded], 1967 (Box 136)
    - Neighborhood board member releases, 1966 (Box 136)
    - Neighborhood board members, committee members, centers, undated (Box 136)
    - Neighborhood board open meeting, 1967 (Box 136)
    - Neighborhood board slates, 1965-1966 (Box 136)
    - Neighborhood board special meetings. Invitations, 1967 (Box 136)
    - Neighborhood board training session, 1965-1966 (Box 136)
    - Newspaper items, 1965-1967 (Box 136)
    - New York telephone bill, 1966 (Box 136)
    - Niagara Mohawk, 1966 (Box 136)
    - Nominating committee, 1965-1966; 2 folders (Box 136)
    - Parental aims, role, 1967 (Box 136)
    - Parental authority, 1967 (Box 136)
    - Parents permission slips, blank, undated (Box 136)
    - Petty cash vouchers, 1965-1967 (Box 136)
    - Physical examination, blanks, 1966 (Box 136)
    - Planning committee, 1966 (Box 136)
    - Planning committee minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 136)
    - Pre-school committee members, 1967 (Box 136)
    - Program coordinator, 1966 (Box 136)
    - Programs operative, undated (Box 136)
    - Railroad car, 1967 (Box 136)
    - Receipts, 1967 (Box 136)
    - Recreation committee, 1966-1967 (Box 136)
    - Remedial reading permission, 1966 (Box 136)
    - Requests for supplies, 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box 137)
    - Requisitions, 1967 (Box 137)
    - Requisitions (filled), 1965-1967 (Box 137)
    - Requisitions forms, 1967 (Box 137)
    - Returned job order forms, 1967 (Box 137)
    - Returned job orders, 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box 137)
    - Salvation Army day camp, undated (Box 137)
    - Six weeks report, 1967 (Box 137)
    - Special meeting minutes, 1967 (Box 137)
    - Staff mailing list, undated (Box 137)
    - Staff meetings, undated (Box 137)
    - Summer jobs (application forms), 1966 (Box 137)
    - Summer preschool program, 1965 (Box 137)
    - Summer programs, 1965-1966; 3 folders (Box 137)
    - Summer program, Catholic Youth organization, 1967 (Box 137)
    - Summer recreation, 1966 (Box 137)
    - Teen council, 1965-1967; 2 folders (Box 137)
    - Thank you notes, 1966-1967 (Box 138)
    - Training correspondence, 1967 (Box 138)
    - Trips, summer program, 1967 (Box 138)
    - Weekly report, 1967 (Box 138)
- Employment Division
  - Financial
    - Expense accounts, procedure, 1965 (Box 138)
    - Home Aides, reasons for budget revision (Box 138)
    - Job Corp, paid invoices, 1965 (Box 357)
    - Neighborhood Youth Corps
      - Bank reconciliations, 1965-1967 (Box 138)
      - Budget report, 1965; 2 folders (Box 138)
      - Budget and financial forms, 1966 (Box 138)
      - Budget, title 1B, 1965 (Box 138)
      - Check stubs out-of-school, Merchants National Bank and Trust Co., 1967 (Box 138)
      - In-kind contribution, 1965-1966; 4 folders (Box 138)
      - Invoices (request for funds), 1967 (Box 138)
      - Journal entries, trial balance, 1965-1967; 13 folders (Box 138)
      - Paid invoices, 1965-1966; 10 folders (Box 139)
      - Payroll, 1965; 2 folders (Box 139)
      - Payroll, 1965; 6 folders (Box 140)
      - Payroll distribution, 1966; 2 folders (Box 140)
      - Payroll list, inschool from 12/66-03/1967, 1966-1967 (Box 140)
      - Records payroll to 4/25/1966, terminations (Box 140)
      - Revised out budget, Jun 1967 (Box 140)
      - Title 1B work papers budget, 1965 (Box 140)
    - On-the-Job Training
      - Bank reconciliations, 1965-1967; 2 folders (Box 140)
      - Financial statements, original, 1964-1965 (Box 140)
      - MD89-64-A, 1964 (Box 140)
      - MD89-64-A, final financial report, 1964-1965; 2 folders (Box 140)
      - Negotiated cost-reimbursement, 1964 (Box 140)
      - Negotiated cost-reimbursement, 1964; 2 folders (Box 141)
      - Paid invoices, 1966 (Box 141)
    - Payroll control, Summer Programs, Jul 1966 (Box 141)
    - Purchase order, job corps, 1966-1967; 5 folders (Box 141)
    - Purchase order log, Summer Programs, 1967 (Box 141)
    - Summer program, packing slips, 1967 (Box 141)
  - Job Corp
    - Contracts, Title 1A OEO, 1965 (Box 141)
    - Facts Parents Should Know About the Job Corps, undated (Box 141)
    - Handbook changes memo, 1965 (Box 141)
    - Handbook for Job Corps screening manuscript, 1965 (Box 141)
    - Job Corps facts, 1965 (Box 141)
    - Job Corps screening handbook, 1965 (Box 141)
    - Office of Economic Opportunity, Job Corps promotional materials, 1965 (Box 141)
    - Referrals, 1966 (Box 141)
    - Screening bulletins, 1967 (Box 141)
    - Special file, 1966 (Box 141)
    - Telegram, 1966 (Box 141)
  - Neighborhood Youth Corps
    - Activity report, 1967 (Box 141)
    - Applications, miscellaneous, 1965; 2 folders (Box 142)
    - Base data, 1966; 5 folders (Box 142)
    - Base data, 1966 (Box 144)
    - Base data forms, posted, not filled, 1965 (Box 144)
    - Checkpoint procedure, 1966 (Box 144)
    - Contract 34-5-030-600, summer school, 1967 (Box 143)
    - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 143)
    - Court actions pending, 1967 (Box 143)
    - Data sheets, 1965; 4 folders (Box 144)
    - Data sheets, formerly enrolled, 1965; 2 folders (Box 144)
    - Disposition request, 1965 (Box 143)
    - Drop outs, undated (Box 143)
    - Employment, 1967; 3 folders (Box 144)
    - Enrollees, 1966 (Box 143)
    - Fact sheet of NYC program, 1967 (Box 357)
    - General, 1966 (Box 143)
    - In school, 1966 (Box 143)
    - Ineligible applicants, 1966 (Box 143)
    - Instructions on filing reports, 1966 (Box 143)
    - Intake data, 1965; 2 folders (Box 145)
    - Intake records, 1965; 2 folders (Box 166)
    - Job questionairre, 1964 (Box 143)
    - Memos, 1965-1966 (Box 143)
    - Monthly reports, 1965-1966; 2 folders (Box 143)
    - New entries, monthly, 1968 (Box 166)
    - NYC policy directive, 1966 (Box 143)
    - NYC program reports, 1965-1967 (Box 143)
    - October report, 1966 (Box 143)
    - Orientation comments, B. Mays, 1968 (Box 143)
    - Pay, 1967 (Box 143)
    - Pending placement, 1967 (Box 143)
    - Personnel files, 1965
      - A, 1965; 19 folders (Box 145)
      - B, 1965; 47 folders (Box 145)
      - C, 1965; 9 folders (Box 145)
      - C, 1965; 34 folders (Box 146)
      - D, 1965; 26 folders (Box 146)
      - E, 1965; 9 folders (Box 146)
      - F, 1965; 23 folders (Box 146)
      - F, 1965; 6 folders (Box 147)
      - G, 1965; 33 folders (Box 147)
      - H, 1965; 28 folders (Box 147)
      - J, 1965; 15 folders (Box 147)
      - K, 1965; 6 folders (Box 147)
      - K, 1965; 10 folders (Box 148)
      - L, 1965; 20 folders (Box 148)
      - M, 1965; 40 folders (Box 148)
      - N, 1965; 5 folders (Box 148)
      - O, 1965; 9 folders (Box 148)
      - P, 1965; 6 folders (Box 148)
      - P, 1965; 33 folders (Box 149)
      - R, 1965; 31 folders (Box 149)
      - S, 1965; 26 folders (Box 149)
      - S, 1965; 30 folders (Box 150)
      - T, 1965; 18 folders (Box 150)
      - U, 1965 (Box 150)
      - V, 1965; 6 folders (Box 150)
      - W, 1965; 30 folders (Box 150)
      - W, 1965; 11 folders (Box 151)
      - Y, 1965 (Box 151)
      - Z, 1965; 5 folders (Box 151)
    - Personnel files, 1966
      - A, 1966; 13 folders (Box 151)
      - B, 1966; 46 folders (Box 151)
      - B, 1966; 27 folders (Box 152)
      - C, 1966; 36 folders (Box 152)
      - C, 1966; 26 folders (Box 153)
      - D, 1966; 51 folders (Box 153)
      - E, 1966; 14 folders (Box 154)
      - F, 1966; 33 folders (Box 154)
      - G, 1966; 20 folders (Box 154)
      - G, 1966; 21 folders (Box 155)
      - H, 1966; 49 folders (Box 155)
      - H, 1966; 20 folders (Box 156)
      - I, 1966; 6 folders (Box 156)
      - J, 1966; 41 folders (Box 156)
      - K, 1966; 10 folders (Box 156)
      - K, 1966; 13 folders (Box 157)
      - L, 1966; 20 folders (Box 157)
      - M, 1966; 30 folders (Box 157)
      - M, 1966; 61 folders (Box 158)
      - N, 1966; 12 folders (Box 158)
      - N, 1966; 2 folders (Box 159)
      - O, 1966; 10 folders (Box 159)
      - P, 1966; 35 folders (Box 159)
      - R, 1966; 14 folders (Box 159)
      - R, 1966; 32 folders (Box 160)
      - S, 1966; 28 folders (Box 160)
      - S, 1966; 58 folders (Box 161)
      - T, 1966; 18 folders (Box 161)
      - T, 1966; 21 folders (Box 162)
      - V, 1966; 14 folders (Box 162)
      - W, 1966; 27 folders (Box 162)
      - W, 1966; 41 folders (Box 163)
      - Y, 1966; 2 folders (Box 163)
      - Z, 1966 (Box 163)
    - Personnel files, applications 1967
      - A, 1967 (Box 163)
      - B, 1967; 2 folders (Box 163)
      - C, 1967 (Box 163)
      - D, 1967 (Box 163)
      - E, 1967 (Box 164)
      - F, 1967 (Box 164)
      - G, 1967 (Box 164)
      - H, 1967 (Box 164)
      - J, 1967 (Box 164)
      - K, 1967 (Box 164)
      - L, 1967 (Box 164)
      - M, 1967 (Box 164)
      - N, 1967 (Box 164)
      - P, 1967 (Box 164)
      - R, 1967 (Box 164)
      - S, 1967 (Box 164)
      - T, 1967 (Box 164)
      - V, 1967 (Box 164)
      - W, 1967 (Box 164)
    - Personnel files, 1967
      - A, 1967 (Box 164)
      - B, 1967; 4 folders (Box 164)
      - B, 1967; 10 folders (Box 165)
      - C, 1967; 4 folders (Box 165)
      - D, 1967; 12 folders (Box 165)
      - E, 1967; 3 folders (Box 165)
      - F, 1967 (Box 165)
      - G, 1967; 9 folders (Box 165)
      - H, 1967; 9 folders (Box 165)
      - J, 1967; 7 folders (Box 165)
      - K, 1967; 2 folders (Box 165)
      - L, 1967; 5 folders (Box 165)
      - M, 1967; 6 folders (Box 165)
      - M, 1967; 14 folders (Box 166)
      - N, 1967 (Box 166)
      - P, 1967; 19 folders (Box 166)
      - S, 1967; 7 folders (Box 166)
      - T, 1967; 4 folders (Box 166)
      - V, 1967; 2 folders (Box 166)
      - W, 1967; 9 folders (Box 166)
    - Program, 1966 (Box 143)
    - Project agreement, 1967 (Box 143)
    - Project budget and funding, 1966 (Box 143)
    - Proposal, 1966; 2 folders (Box 168)
    - Record of eligibility determination, 1965 (Box 168)
    - Recruiters aid meeting, 1966 (Box 168)
    - Referral and enrollment action, 1965; 5 folders (Box 167)
    - Referral and enrollment action, data sheets, 1965; 2 folders (Box 167)
    - Referral and enrollment action, data sheets voided, 1965 (Box 167)
    - Referral and enrollment action, In-school Special Summer program, 1965 (Box 167)
    - Referral and enrollment action, In-school Special Summer program, 1965; 3 folders (Box 167)
    - Referral and enrollment action, In-school Special Summer program, 1965 (Box 183)
    - Reports, data, Sep 1965 (Box 168)
    - Special report, 1965-1966 (Box 168)
    - Sponser's invoice and payroll reports, 1965-1967; 2 folders (Box 168)
    - Team staffing meeting minutes, 1968 (Box 168)
    - Ten numbers assigned by employment, 1966 (Box 168)
    - Top Cat newspaper, 1966 (Box 168)
    - US Department of Labor, Manpower, Neighborhood Youth Corps, 1965 (Box 168)
  - Staff files
    - Alex Humphrey files
      - Applications, 1967 (Box 186)
      - Cancelled material requests, 1966 (Box 186)
      - Correspondence, incoming, 1967; 3 folders (Box 186)
      - Memos, incoming, 1966 (Box 186)
      - Mimeograph job orders, 1967 (Box 186)
      - Personal, 1967 (Box 186)
      - Program policy memos, 1967 (Box 186)
      - Purchase orders received, 1967 (Box 186)
  - Training programs
    - Applications, intake, 1965; 4 folders (Box 183)
    - Attendance record, 1967; 7 folders (Box 168)
    - Base data, 1964-1966; 5 folders (Box 169)
    - Base data, change of status, 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box 169)
    - Base data, change of status, 1966-1967; 6 folders (Box 170)
    - Base data, change of status, 1966-1967; 7 folders (Box 171)
    - Base data, employment, 1966 (Box 172)
    - Base data, employment, inschool summer program, 1967 (Box 172)
    - Base data, employment, summer program, 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box 172)
    - Characteristics of trainees, MT101, 1964; 5 folders (Box 172)
    - Characteristics of trainees under the MDTA and the ARA, MT101, 1965 (Box 172)
    - Characteristics of trainees under the MDTA and the ARA, MT101, disposition of youth, 1965 (Box 183)
    - Clerical program
      - Clerical report, 1967 (Box 173)
      - Individual progress sheet, 1967 (Box 173)
      - Speed timings, 1967 (Box 173)
      - Trisdale White typing, undated (Box 173)
    - Discussion of skill training and remedial education program [photos], 1964 (Box 173)
    - Discussion of on-the-job training program, undated (Box 173)
    - Division reports, 1966 (Box 173)
    - Employee attendance record
      - Jacqueline Piper, 1965 (Box 173)
      - Judith Garvey, 1965 (Box 173)
      - Patricia Pearson, 1965 (Box 173)
      - Patricia La Casse, 1965 (Box 173)
    - Employment forms, 1966 (Box 173)
    - Employment task force, 1966 (Box 173)
    - Employment workstations-in-school and direct placements, 1967; 2 folders (Box 173)
    - Evaluation reports, 1967 (Box 173)
    - Fact sheet, 1965 (Box 173)
    - Information on summer programs, 1967 (Box 174)
    - In-school roster, 1968 (Box 174)
    - In-service training, 1967 (Box 174)
    - In-serrvice training memos, 1966 (Box 174)
    - In-service training program, 1966 (Box 174)
    - In-service training, William Streets, 1967 (Box 174)
    - Intake data and On-the-Job referrals, Nov 1965 (Box 174)
    - Manpower Development and Training program, 1966 (Box 174)
    - Manpower program, facts about the pre-employment program, 1967
    - Manpower staff, in-service training, 1967 (Box 174)
    - Monthly attendance, Dec 1967 (Box 174)
    - OMAT monthly reports, 1966 (Box 357)
    - On-the-Job list/terminations, 1966 (Box 174)
    - On-the-Job intake forms, evaluations, 1964; 2 folders (Box 174)
    - On-the-Job training applications, contracts with Mayor's Commission for Youth, 1964 (Box 174)
    - On-the-Job training MDS9-64A contract, 1963-1964 (Box 174)
    - Payroll roster, 1967; 12 folders (Box 174)
    - Personnel files
      - A, 1965; 16 folders (Box 175)
      - B, 1965; 50 folders (Box 175)
      - C, 1965; 41 folders (Box 175)
      - D, 1965; 30 folders (Box 176)
      - E, 1965; 9 folders (Box 176)
      - F, 1965; 22 folders (Box 176)
      - G, 1965; 22 folders (Box 176)
      - G, 1965; 13 folders (Box 177)
      - H, 1965; 36 folders (Box 177)
      - J, 1965; 18 folders (Box 177)
      - K, 1965; 13 folders (Box 177)
      - L, 1965; 11 folders (Box 177)
      - L, 1965; 8 folders (Box 178)
      - M, 1965; 54 folders (Box 178)
      - N, 1965; 8 folders (Box 178)
      - O, 1965; 10 folders (Box 178)
      - P, 1965; 9 folders (Box 178)
      - P, 1965; 32 folders (Box 179)
      - R, 1965; 18 folders (Box 179)
      - S, 1965; 24 folders (Box 179)
      - S, 1965; 35 folders (Box 180)
      - T, 1965; 24 folders (Box 180)
      - U, 1965 (Box 180)
      - V, 1965; 6 folders (Box 180)
      - W, 1965; 28 folders (Box 180)
      - W, 1965; 16 folders (Box 181)
      - Y, 1965; 3 folders (Box 181)
      - Z, 1965; 6 folders (Box 181)
      - Youth Workers, 1966-1967; 10 folders (Box 181)
      - Youth Workers, 1966; 13 folders (Box 182)
      - Youth Workers, 1965-1966; 6 folders (Box 183)
    - Phone lists, 1966-1967 (Box 357)
    - Police training program, 1965 (Box 357)
    - Program fact sheet, 1965 (Box 357)